{
    "id": "d2c9aa9257834341b8f6d245da5e6910",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He wants to know if he ……………………….. a promotion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would get",
                "will get",
                "shall get"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eee2ac5d7b25442cb0c64ddf8c09344e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I remarked how lovely …………………………….",
            "description": "In exclamations the subject goes before the auxiliary verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "was she",
                "she was",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "69758d6ace74480a91938f633eaaa00a"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had any money, I ……………………………. you a gift.",
            "description": "In the second conditional we use a simple past in the if clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "will buy",
                "would buy",
                "would have bought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db1a44d7b7dc4477a88953ca646d96f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know how many books ……………………………. written.",
            "description": "In reported questions the subject goes before the auxiliary verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "she has",
                "has she"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a46d6825ab4c4a0ea47cfb55bd354288"
        },
        {
            "question": "She seemed ………………………… about something.",
            "description": "Seem is a copular verb. We use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "angry",
                "angrily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e6029b1d38149ad85d8860369fd1069"
        },
        {
            "question": "I spoke to a woman who …………………………. the chairperson.",
            "description": "We use seem to be before noun phrases.",
            "answers": [
                "seemed",
                "seemed to be",
                "seemed as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8dcc5e83fc934d45b808e07cb7b32a1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we were kids we …………………………….. hours watching TV.",
            "description": "Would is used to talk about past habits.",
            "answers": [
                "will spend",
                "would spend",
                "should spend"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bacbb383a2642a985bd1c7d3672f4df"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody …………………………. wear seat belts.",
            "description": "Should shows obligation.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c503f710335d4c529096cd53d8183ba5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you like some help?",
            "description": "You cannot say ‘should you like…?’",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a4e287d4e96429b9b574da1bf1fe901"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………….. be here soon. He left office at five.",
            "description": "Should is used to talk about logical possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7aa5f05e28fd474996d4149150e433a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Applications …………………………. be sent before Friday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bc394b6a17c942839b0e7c9ca9982cc1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. have called him in the morning, but I forgot.",
            "description": "Should is used with a perfect infinitive to talk about past events that did not happen.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b08e9ff23b9e4513b186e2a68127bdec"
        }
    ]
}